[Music]
icici lombard and cnbc tv 18 present
india risk management awards risk master
class
over the years we have positioned
ourselves as risk solution provider
and not just an insurer who provides you
with coverage capacity and settles the
claims past
with this endeavor we have introduced
marine transit risk
prevention activity iot for fire
hydrants
wellness solution in health space
virtual risk assessment
using drones and many more
this approach has led to reduction of
claims
and has been really appreciated by our
customers icici lombard
and cnbc tv 18 present india risk
management awards
risk master class